Guide to the Stanford University, Radio Astronomy Institute, records SC1313
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Radio Astronomy Institute, records
1965-1978
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University. Radio Astronomy Institute
SC1313
3 Linear Feet
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research use; materials must be requested at least 48 hours in advance of intended use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Administrative transfer, 2016.
Scope and Contents
Collection of GLINTS (internal reports) of the Stanford Radio Astronomy Institute. Many GLINTS are first drafts of published papers.
Astronomy.; Radio astronomy; Stanford University. Radio Astronomy Institute
- Records, Accession ARCH-2017-100
  - Observatory Reports & Index, undated (Box 1)
  - User's Guide: Stanford Five-Element Interferometer Operating Manual, 1973 Dec (Box 1)
  - Radio Astronomy Institute - Shadows & Glints, Vol I, No. 1-100, 1961-165 (Box 1)
  - Radio Astronomy Institute Glints, Vol II, No. 101-199, 1965-1967 (Box 1)
  - Radio Astronomy Institute Glints, Vol III, No. 200-299, 1967-1969 (Box 1)
  - Stanford Radio Astronomy Institute Glints 300-399, vol. IV, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
  - Stanford Radio Astronomy Institute Glints 400-499, vol. V, 1971-1973 (Box 2)
  - Stanford Radio Astronomy Institute Glints vol. VI, 1972-1977 (Box 2)
  - Stanford Radio Astronomy Institute Glints vol. VII, 1977-1978 (Box 2)